[Music]
how about usually the last consistent
schoolyard football
I mean sometimes there was a kid on
crutches and I think second Alaska like
it taught me I'm never gonna be a pro
football player when I grew up and that
was a valuable lesson
and that's something today's kids aren't
learning political revolution trending
horse I am on the wrong side of a
cultural war Elysee hungers worth the
food school after 1918 the school
diversity is imagining everybody come
protest was me trying to frame yourself
as an underdog in your one nation under
let their guard on major story shut up
and fight for glory don't slow down
until we grow and you write the course
of his story our hip-hop and make new
protest songs some of y'all can rap a
longer ski stand individually storm pack
that bond light it up and hold it down
to this crap is gone
believe me greatness yup we don't have
to take this let's break taboos make
niggas we're dropping this chemical
signal be back and Woodstock let's
broadcast passion and energy with the
media belongs to the enemy what Annie
come by rappers eat enemy you're not one
of them so to pretend to be peaceably
and briefly stand up it's a little speck
of me unless you're a hypocritical
histor fuck on a Mac PC
put up with this shit for too long
I'm Rich's fucking your shit soft if you
went to college you got ripped off they
told police and go fuck off if you went
to college got ripped off then I get
that mixed y'all pissed off the tone
police you go fuck off if you went to
college got ripped off then I get that
mixed up pissed off